应该有这么个世界
There's a world that should be real somewhere
缺少紧张，爱遍世间
There's a lack of tension and love to spare
真希望我曾经去过
I would tell you that I'd been before
它就在逐梦之门身后
It was just behind the dreamer's door
就在逐梦之门身后
Just behind the dreamer's door
如画般的地和七彩般的天
Painted hills and colored skies
那儿的景色绝对会你惊艳
A wondrous view that simply strikes the heart
有人负责高挂满天星
There's one who holds the stars in place
有人负责撑起整片天
Another who keeps it all from falling apart
每天走著一样的规律
The same routine runs every day
但他们就是这样
but that's just who they are
那堵墙外头的生活
Life outside of the wall
只希望我曾经梦过
I could say I'd dreamed it
我只要一次，但老实说
real one time, if at all
我也很难说没有过
I could hardly tell you
会认识谁，会见到什么
Who's to know, what you'll find
我知道它就在那儿
But it's there, I'm sure
你想要的不过
What you're looking for is
就在逐梦之门身后
just behind the dreamer's door
有人总是工作到傍晚
There's one who works until sundown
有人总能看到你的美
Another who sees the beauty in everyone
他呀，把天空视为心肺
This one takes the sky to heart
这位则乐子永远找不完
The other one knows the best ways to have fun
安静的她虽还很迷茫
The quiet one's still searching but
她已找到她的志向
she knows who she'll become
那堵墙外头的生活
Life outside of the wall
只希望我曾经梦过
I could say I'd dreamed it
我只要一次，但老实说
real one time, if at all
我也很难说没有过
I could hardly tell you
会认识谁，会见到什么
Who's to know, what you'll find
我知道它就在那儿
But it's there, I'm sure
你想要的不过
What you're looking for is
就在逐梦之门身后
just behind the dreamer's door
张开眼，自己看
Open up, take a look
你绝对不会相信
You will never believe it
向前进，迎著风
Take a step, feel the air
珍惜你眼前所见
Cherish what you see
有位女孩总想做到最好
There's a girl who wants to do her best
到完美前她都不会睡觉
'Til she has it, she won't stop or rest
不知道它会藏著什么
Doesn't know just what there is in store
逐梦之门身后有什么
What there is behind the dreamer's door
就在逐梦之门身后
Just behind the dreamer's door